puresight.com 2006-06-15

# PureSight - Intelligent Content Recognition for wired and mobile networks

Privacy Statement

**Last Updated: January 15, 2004**  
PURESIGHT Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read this privacy policy.

Collection of your Personal Information  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are purchasing, registering a purchase of, ordering or installing PURESIGHT products. Personal information collected by PURESIGHT may include e-mail address, language, country or location, address, telephone number and credit card number, if necessary for the services or products you requested. PureSight also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of PureSight.

Use of your Personal Information  
We use your personal information for the following purposes 

  * To ensure our site is relevant to your needs.
  * To deliver services, such as newsletters, events, training or software, that you request or purchase.
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from PURESIGHT, if you so request.
  * We will merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. PURESIGHT may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on PURESIGHT or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of PureSight, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of PURESIGHT employees, users of PURESIGHT products or services, or members of the public. Your information may be stored and processed in any country in which PURESIGHT or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. PURESIGHT strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, PURESIGHT intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your information.

Control of your Personal Information  
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, PURESIGHT will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

Access to your Personal Information  
We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. If you register on our site or subscribe to a newsletter, you can review and edit your personal information.

Security of your Personal Information  
PURESIGHT is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

Use of Cookies  
When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above. We also use cookies to collect information on which newsletter links are clicked by customers. This information is used to ensure we are sending information customers want to read. It is collected in aggregate form and never linked with your personal information. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the PURESIGHT Web site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site.

Your Consent  
By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to PURESIGHT's processing of personal information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where PURESIGHT collects personal information on the Web site.

Changes to this Statement  
PURESIGHT will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, PURESIGHT will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.

Contact Information  
PURESIGHT welcomes your comments regarding this privacy policy by [email](mailto:support@puresight.com)

|   
---|---
